/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7bc4b30e99eeabcd4303"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-being-a-lawyer-as-awesome-as-it-looks-on-Suits?-",
    "answer" : "Dave Cheng Unfortunately, no. While there are parts of being a lawyer that can involve some of the glamorous aspects highlighted in the show (for example, helping people in need through pro bono work, winning an intellectual contest against the adverse party in litigation, or \"winning\" a transactional matter by obtaining more value for your client than she had anticipated), there is also a great deal of detail-oriented and much less interesting work and also potentially significant adverse impact on your personal life. Awesome or Potentially Awesome Features of BigLaw Suits does depict some awesome or potentially awesome aspects of BigLaw, so I thought I'd start with the good news. One of the reasonably accurate depictions of a positive aspect of BigLaw is the high pay and the fancy perks surrounding t Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:29:39.828Z"),
    "question" : "Is being a lawyer as awesome as it looks on Suits? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7bf0b30e99eeabcd430e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-become-a-lawyer-as-a-career-change?-",
    "answer" : "I was a career change lawyer. I loved my night school class - one physician, one retired Navy nuke submarine officer, a bunch of cops and me. I sport a blue T-shirt in my 1993 law school ID photo. I laughed every time I took a glimpse. I attended law school - day two ( I arrogantly skipped day one)- straight from the Philadelphia Airport where I had just led a HazMat response to an unknown leaking drum. Night school, day school, online - the options are endless. Caution - go to law school only because the pain of NOT being a lawyer is unbearable. 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:30:24.169Z"),
    "question" : "How do I become a lawyer as a career change? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7c0db30e99eeabcd431a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-was-your-best-moment-as-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "A few years back, I was asked to become involved with and, if possible, take over a case against an insurance company that was facing a motion to dismiss that had some teeth to it. I dug deep into the law, learned all about the arcane history of “standard loss payees,” and fought off the motion and the case moved out of the gates. The more I dug into the case, the more I concluded that the insurer’s efforts to deny coverage were ill conceived and that even the insurer did not believe in the merits of their position. Additionally, the insurer invoked about 20 tactics to discourage and intimidate and belittle our client from moving forward with the claim. I amended the complaint to assert, not just the insurance claim, but bad faith, rife with hundreds of paragraphs of details. The insurer den Continue Reading A few years back, I was asked to become involved with and, if possible, take over a case against an insurance company that was facing a motion to dismiss that had some teeth to it. I dug deep into the law, learned all about the arcane history of “standard loss payees,” and fought off the motion and the case moved out of the gates. The more I dug into the case, the more I concluded that the insurer’s efforts to deny coverage were ill conceived and that even the insurer did not believe in the merits of their position. Additionally, the insurer invoked about 20 tactics to discourage and intimidate and belittle our client from moving forward with the claim. I amended the complaint to assert, not just the insurance claim, but bad faith, rife with hundreds of paragraphs of details. The insurer den Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:30:53.688Z"),
    "question" : "What was your best moment as a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7c48b30e99eeabcd4328"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-it-working-in-corporate-law-as-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "Bright, interesting, fulfilling, glamaros, Money-minting. Depressing, unfriendly, brawlish, dissatisfactory, miserly paying. It all depends on your perception, and times. One day, you will feel one way, and the other way on other times.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:31:52.998Z"),
    "question" : "How is it working in corporate law as a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7c5ab30e99eeabcd432d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-perks-of-being-a-female-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "A great benefit to human causes everywhere would be if peoples stopped asking pseudo- significant Q like that. Significance is significance. If you'd asker what are the benefits of people of honor becoming attorneys, I would have been willing to help you specifically with all kinds of issues. Honor is more important than gender, color, age, orientation, etc. Until we phrase our individual and collective questions on integrity and altruism, we're doomed to endless worship at the cult of me, me, me. Debra Stewart! Clayburn Griffin",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:32:10.884Z"),
    "question" : "What are the perks of being a female lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7c8ab30e99eeabcd4338"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-most-painful-lesson-you-learned-as-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "People lie. They lie to their lawyers, they lie to the courts, they lie to each other. Spouses lie to each other—parents lie to children. Judges lie to courtrooms. Clients, too often, want something for nothing. They swear they will pay their bills—about two-thirds even make the attempt. Way too many people are willing to cause pain and hurt to others in return for even the slightest possible benefits to themselves. They don’t even begin to think of how their actions will impact those around them. People are far too willing to push the difficult decisions away. Parents leave vexing financial difficulties to their children to solve. Parties would rather dissolve a marriage and punish their children than take even simple steps to try and repair their relationships. Prosecutors and police misuse the Continue Reading People lie. They lie to their lawyers, they lie to the courts, they lie to each other. Spouses lie to each other—parents lie to children. Judges lie to courtrooms. Clients, too often, want something for nothing. They swear they will pay their bills—about two-thirds even make the attempt. Way too many people are willing to cause pain and hurt to others in return for even the slightest possible benefits to themselves. They don’t even begin to think of how their actions will impact those around them. People are far too willing to push the difficult decisions away. Parents leave vexing financial difficulties to their children to solve. Parties would rather dissolve a marriage and punish their children than take even simple steps to try and repair their relationships. Prosecutors and police misuse the Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:32:58.129Z"),
    "question" : "What is the most painful lesson you learned as a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7ca0b30e99eeabcd433f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-pros-and-cons-of-being-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "I'm a civil litigator who goes to trial fairly often. I can't speak for all lawyers, but for me…. Pros: I learn new things frequently. Usually it's information I wouldn't learn any other way, such as how an automatic revolving door works or how fishing habits have changed over the last decade.I feel good about helping my clients. They are people who wish they never met me (nobody wants to get sued), but I am regularly thanked by them for the work I do. Often I get hugs, kind words, even thank you cards. Minimally, I hope I have made a stressful situation easier to bear.I enjoy the challenge. Almost every time I work on a case, there is a skillful opponent who is waiting to score points against me. The work is fast-paced and requires me to listen and think on my feet. I am convinced that my wContinue Reading I'm a civil litigator who goes to trial fairly often. I can't speak for all lawyers, but for me…. Pros: I learn new things frequently. Usually it's information I wouldn't learn any other way, such as how an automatic revolving door works or how fishing habits have changed over the last decade.I feel good about helping my clients. They are people who wish they never met me (nobody wants to get sued), but I am regularly thanked by them for the work I do. Often I get hugs, kind words, even thank you cards. Minimally, I hope I have made a stressful situation easier to bear.I enjoy the challenge. Almost every time I work on a case, there is a skillful opponent who is waiting to score points against me. The work is fast-paced and requires me to listen and think on my feet. I am convinced that my wContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:33:20.725Z"),
    "question" : "What are the pros and cons of being a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7cb9b30e99eeabcd4346"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-be-a-fashion-designer-and-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "HI, Let me start by asking you something? If you will do both, when people ask you “What do you do for a living” what will your answer be?? Are you a lawyer or a fashion designer? It is not easy, but maybe you can manage if you find the answer to this question: Which will be your job and which will be your hobby? To do both as a job I don’t think so!  Somewhere you will have to put your soul, to go the extra mile! The rest are only hobbies.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:33:45.689Z"),
    "question" : "Can I be a fashion designer and a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7ce5b30e99eeabcd4352"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-are-so-many-lawyers-unhappy-with-their-jobs?-",
    "answer" : "Barsha Banerjee In India the scenario can be decided into two groups. 1. Those in corporate sector as Corporate lawyers. 2. Those in litigation. 1. The corporate sectors generally hires lawyers from National Law Schools and at the end of their degree they have campusing which offers jobs. The colleges motivates students for internships (some of them are paid and some unpaid) during their semesters. This helps in gaining experience and becoming a professional at an early stage. Moreover the secured job that campusing offers is much lucrative but work pressure is also heavy. 2. The ones in litigation are generally from government law colleges. The teaching pattern is very traditional here. No internship and campusing. It's basically up to the student to figure out his way of both practical learning and earnin Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:34:29.036Z"),
    "question" : "Why are so many lawyers unhappy with their jobs? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7d0bb30e99eeabcd435c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-being-a-lawyer-a-good-occupation-to-pursue?-",
    "answer" : "Elizabeth Anne Marshall I am willing to bet that most professions for which you have an abundant amount of dedicated tv series (lawyers, forensics, criminal investigators, writers etc) are very likely a lot less glamorous than you'd expect, and that actually, you are more unlikely to get anything you'd expect out of it: less money, less thrill, less everything.  I say this on the assumption that you are not directly familiar with the profession (eg. internship), nor are you somewhat tangent to it (it runs in the family/ you've experienced something about it directly), but are inspired by \"cool\" tv series, literature and media portrails of lawyers, law firms and how awesome it is to be a lawyer.  It very much depends on which country you plan to practice law. I think that one of the most magical places for the legal Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:35:07.427Z"),
    "question" : "Is being a lawyer a good occupation to pursue? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7d33b30e99eeabcd4366"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-most-rewarding-part-about-being-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "Bobby Strickland Taking on the responsibility of a Barrister is a huge undertaking. The unbiased mind must always be so that the rule of law may be a statement of integrity. One that stands firm for the freedoms of our rights as a free people. Lawyers are held to a specific scrutiny which means they have guidelines in which they shall dress, file motions or briefs in which to best represent everyone. Do all the holders of the Juris Prudence follow each guideline... No, sadly there are a handful which will take short cuts to attempt to do the Potomac two step ( political side step ) trying to beat the system by cheating the courts or the people they represent. They are of little moral character and only wish to move on to the next defendant or civil matter. The upside of being a lawyer is that this position Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:35:47.670Z"),
    "question" : "What is the most rewarding part about being a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7d49b30e99eeabcd4370"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-you-know-if-a-lawyer-is-good?-",
    "answer" : "John Martin Sujay, Self Employed at Advocacy (2016-present)Answered December 3, 2020 · Author has 6.4K answers and 2.7M answer viewsHow do you know if a lawyer is good? John Martin Sujay How to make out which lawyer is best for your case, I'll guide you ! First you need to select a good ADVOCATE ! Who is good ADVOCATE???? This one is good ADVOCATE 👇 Usually court case should be over within four dates. Maximum 7 dates. If any advocate is is getting your case resolved and decided within 7 days from the date of filing the case. Then that advocate is a good advocate. Keep the above the measure and find advocate yourself by going to the court premises or the bar association. No advocate will refer anybody to anyone. If I refer you to some advocate in Bangalore. If that advocate does not perform well and the case will go on for years without any end, you will curse him.and also curse me. If you don't pay him proper fees. He will curse me for referring you to him. I don't want to get into  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:36:09.226Z"),
    "question" : "How do you know if a lawyer is good? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7d5cb30e99eeabcd4376"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-become-a-doctor-or-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "I had this same dilemma in high school. I don't remember how I made the decision to be a lawyer, but I was quite young when I did. I had been taking all of the classes that would have prepared me for law school, speech classes, history, joined all the right clubs, went to Boy’s State in Illinois. I excelled in all of these areas. Then I injured my back. I could no longer do sports without continually re-injuring myself. I went to a chiropractor when I was unable to walk and he was able to get me back on my feet. It just so happens that my best friend’s uncle was also a chiropractor and Rich was also going into that field. This was when I questioned if I really was meant to be a lawyer. I had decided to make an appointment with some lawyers in my small town of 14,000 and some appointments wi Continue Reading I had this same dilemma in high school. I don't remember how I made the decision to be a lawyer, but I was quite young when I did. I had been taking all of the classes that would have prepared me for law school, speech classes, history, joined all the right clubs, went to Boy’s State in Illinois. I excelled in all of these areas. Then I injured my back. I could no longer do sports without continually re-injuring myself. I went to a chiropractor when I was unable to walk and he was able to get me back on my feet. It just so happens that my best friend’s uncle was also a chiropractor and Rich was also going into that field. This was when I questioned if I really was meant to be a lawyer. I had decided to make an appointment with some lawyers in my small town of 14,000 and some appointments wi Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:36:28.819Z"),
    "question" : "Should I become a doctor or lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7d6fb30e99eeabcd437c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Do-you-regret-becoming-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "I have been a lawyer for 7 years now, and deciding to practice law was the best decision I ever made, but I attribute my satisfaction to each of the following factors (relevant only to private practice, which is the only experience I have): I do not mind long hours, so long as I am well compensated. Many lawyers dislike the hours (my experience is with folks at large law firms), but I knew going into big-law that long hours are part of the package. If the hours start to bug you, you can go into government or certain in-house roles. I did not have law school loans, but even if I did, the pay in big-law is so good that I would have paid them off in a year.Interest in subject matter: Having majored in science, I chose patent law, which allowed me to stay within science, learn tons of new conceContinue Reading I have been a lawyer for 7 years now, and deciding to practice law was the best decision I ever made, but I attribute my satisfaction to each of the following factors (relevant only to private practice, which is the only experience I have): I do not mind long hours, so long as I am well compensated. Many lawyers dislike the hours (my experience is with folks at large law firms), but I knew going into big-law that long hours are part of the package. If the hours start to bug you, you can go into government or certain in-house roles. I did not have law school loans, but even if I did, the pay in big-law is so good that I would have paid them off in a year.Interest in subject matter: Having majored in science, I chose patent law, which allowed me to stay within science, learn tons of new conceContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:36:47.318Z"),
    "question" : "Do you regret becoming a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7daeb30e99eeabcd438a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-being-a-lawyer-a-good-career-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Abhishek Sinh (अभिषेक सिंह/ابھیشیک سنگھ), works at Government of IndiaAnswered 1 year ago · Author has 55 answers and 103.7K answer viewsIs being a lawyer a good career in India? Abhishek Sinh (अभिषेक सिंह/ابھیشیک سنگھ) Yes, definitely, being a lawyer is a good career option in India. There are lots of career avenues for a lawyer in India, namely: Civil Judge (Junior Division) exams organised by State PSCs for appointment of judges in the subordinate courts within the state.Central and state govt. also nominates advocates to represent them in District Courts, High Courts, Supreme Court and other tribunals.Advocates also have an opportunity of being directly appointed as a judge in High Courts and Supreme Court.Law officer exams of PSUs/PSBs offering the post of officer or assistant manager in executive grade.Short service commission in the Indian Army in the Judge Advocate General Branch/Law Cadre in the Indian Navy and Indian Air Force.Higher studies in law field include LLM degree and thereafter a doctorContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:37:50.800Z"),
    "question" : "Is being a lawyer a good career in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7dc3b30e99eeabcd4390"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-be-a-lawyer-or-pilot?-",
    "answer" : "Sara Olson We have a problem. Our law schools are churning out new law school graduates every year, and very few of those graduates ever find a job in the legal profession. WHY? Because there are not enough legal positions available. If you wish to practice law, you can try to get a job at a big law firm. Or you can make a sign to put in your yard to advertise your “new practice” of law, and be self-employed. I have heard only about 5% of new law graduates actually find jobs in big law firms. So you have to be on the top of your class. And plan to work 60–70 hours per week for a fairly moderate salary. Or maybe you could do some paralegal work? Starting a new law practice doesn’t pay, unless you can get lots of new cases, and settle them fast enough to pay your bills. Before you decide to go to law school Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:38:11.302Z"),
    "question" : "Should I be a lawyer or pilot? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7dfab30e99eeabcd43a0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Would-being-a-lawyer-help-me-to-embrace-a-career-as-an-entrepreneur?-",
    "answer" : "Mark Schneider, Business ConsultantAnswered 6 years ago · Author has 1.5K answers and 2.5M answer viewsWould being a lawyer help me to embrace a career as an entrepreneur? Mark Schneider Being an entrepreneur is a mindset to see opportunities and combining resources to achieve the goals you have set. An academic degree will help you to jump some learning processes that entrepreneurs go through called trial and error, because you will know in advance what works and does not work.  Being a lawyer in a certain field might help you to have a deeper insight and construct certain deals in certain investment/finance related industries that might not have not been possible with just a business degree. It all depends were and with what you want to work starting your own business. Its about the product/business idea you want to create and where you know exactly what you want to do. The rest in business related academics you can just learn via books.  When it comes to normal business, Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:39:06.879Z"),
    "question" : "Would being a lawyer help me to embrace a career as an entrepreneur? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7e3cb30e99eeabcd43b2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-law-not-a-good-career-option-anymore?-",
    "answer" : "Any career is good if you work hard enough to gather the necessary skills to perform jobs in a particular career , now coming to law …law is everywhere like literally everywhere - contracts , agreements , protection , deal structures etc you name anything in the world it will have legal aspects related to it ! Law offers you goverment jobs as law officers in various government departments even in PSU's and also one can attempt state judicial services examinations after which one can be civil judge a respectable position of the judiciary with good salary now coming to corporate world law has evolved alot in this area and will continue evolving , numerous corporate law firms are there which work with huge corporations to get their deals done or draft complex high stake contracts for them and Continue Reading Any career is good if you work hard enough to gather the necessary skills to perform jobs in a particular career , now coming to law …law is everywhere like literally everywhere - contracts , agreements , protection , deal structures etc you name anything in the world it will have legal aspects related to it ! Law offers you goverment jobs as law officers in various government departments even in PSU's and also one can attempt state judicial services examinations after which one can be civil judge a respectable position of the judiciary with good salary now coming to corporate world law has evolved alot in this area and will continue evolving , numerous corporate law firms are there which work with huge corporations to get their deals done or draft complex high stake contracts for them and Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:40:12.639Z"),
    "question" : "Is law not a good career option anymore? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7e71b30e99eeabcd43c3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-three-most-important-things-to-do-in-order-to-be-a-successful-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "What steps should I take to become a successful lawyer? There is no step by step guide available for you to follow, however, below is what I can tell you through my experience. Trial court If you are pursuing your law degree right now then it is the best time you should start assisting a lawyer at your convenient times, this way you will have a practical knowledge, which will of course help you through your course and by the time you would complete your degree, you will have the comprehensive knowledge of legal procedures, which will give you a head start towards your independent practice. For those who have already enrolled as an advocate then trial court should be the first place to start with. Choose a senior in your favourable field and start becoming helpful to him / her. The more they ex Continue Reading What steps should I take to become a successful lawyer? There is no step by step guide available for you to follow, however, below is what I can tell you through my experience. Trial court If you are pursuing your law degree right now then it is the best time you should start assisting a lawyer at your convenient times, this way you will have a practical knowledge, which will of course help you through your course and by the time you would complete your degree, you will have the comprehensive knowledge of legal procedures, which will give you a head start towards your independent practice. For those who have already enrolled as an advocate then trial court should be the first place to start with. Choose a senior in your favourable field and start becoming helpful to him / her. The more they ex Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:41:05.620Z"),
    "question" : "What are the three most important things to do in order to be a successful lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7e96b30e99eeabcd43ce"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-way-for-a-poor-person-to-become-rich?-Should-they-go-down-traditionally-high-paying-career-paths-(doctor,-lawyer,-investment-banker,-computer-scientist)?-",
    "answer" : "The best way to become and stay rich is the same no matter how grandiose or meager your beginnings.  Spend less than you make.Save a portion of your income.Invest your time and money wisely.Use debt as a tool.  If you can't use it wisely then don't use it at all.Corollary: If you take a debt that will not decrease your future expenses or increase your future revenue, you aren't using debt as a tool.  It's using you, tool. One more specifically for those in and entering college:You pay to college to learn marketable skills.  It is an investment.  Before you spend years of salary and years of life on a degree make sure the skills you receive will be marketable and worth what they cost. Is that culinary arts degree worth  $33,000?What jobs will that a $88,000 graphic arts degree get you?  Did Continue Reading The best way to become and stay rich is the same no matter how grandiose or meager your beginnings.  Spend less than you make.Save a portion of your income.Invest your time and money wisely.Use debt as a tool.  If you can't use it wisely then don't use it at all.Corollary: If you take a debt that will not decrease your future expenses or increase your future revenue, you aren't using debt as a tool.  It's using you, tool. One more specifically for those in and entering college:You pay to college to learn marketable skills.  It is an investment.  Before you spend years of salary and years of life on a degree make sure the skills you receive will be marketable and worth what they cost. Is that culinary arts degree worth  $33,000?What jobs will that a $88,000 graphic arts degree get you?  Did Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:41:42.491Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best way for a poor person to become rich? Should they go down traditionally high-paying career paths (doctor, lawyer, investment banker, computer scientist)? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7ea8b30e99eeabcd43d4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-subjects-should-I-take-to-become-a-criminal-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "Jeffrey Price This is a nutshell crime scene in a dollhouse used by crime scene investigators over the years. The picture doesn’t do it justice - you need to see all of them in person if you can. The point of this diorama was to get investigators to look, study and discern clues. As a criminal lawyer-to-be you have to be part investigator, part legal-eagle, part showman, and part story teller. You need people skills, the ability to show empathy, writing skills and an open mind. People will lie to you directly. They will tell you what you want to hear, or what they want you to hear and they will lie through omission. What undergraduate classes can you take that will provide you with all those disparate skill sets? Let’s examine the major things you will deal with: Police reports - literature (both modern an Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:42:00.585Z"),
    "question" : "What subjects should I take to become a criminal lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7edeb30e99eeabcd43e5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-make-a-career-as-an-IPR-lawyer-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Greetings, Nice Question. Step by Step Answer to your Question: To understand the answer, first you need to know process to becoming Patent Attorney and IPR attorney in India→ Patent Attorney→ In India,Patent Attorney can be termed as IPR Attorney, IP Attorney but vice versa is not possible. Patent Attorney can handle all the tasks related to Patents including Litigation part. Process to becoming a Patent Attorney in India → According to my research there are two types of Patent Attorneys in India, You can search on the web repository for more information.I will not responsible for any action taken by you after reading this answer. Registered Patent Attorneys. (Type 1)Edit 1. “Eligibility: a. Degree in Engineering, Science or Technology. b. And Registered as an Advocate in Advocate Act 1961 of India  Continue Reading Greetings, Nice Question. Step by Step Answer to your Question: To understand the answer, first you need to know process to becoming Patent Attorney and IPR attorney in India→ Patent Attorney→ In India,Patent Attorney can be termed as IPR Attorney, IP Attorney but vice versa is not possible. Patent Attorney can handle all the tasks related to Patents including Litigation part. Process to becoming a Patent Attorney in India → According to my research there are two types of Patent Attorneys in India, You can search on the web repository for more information.I will not responsible for any action taken by you after reading this answer. Registered Patent Attorneys. (Type 1)Edit 1. “Eligibility: a. Degree in Engineering, Science or Technology. b. And Registered as an Advocate in Advocate Act 1961 of India  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:42:54.466Z"),
    "question" : "How do I make a career as an IPR lawyer in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7ef1b30e99eeabcd43eb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-facts-I-should-know-before-studying-to-be-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "Dan Rosenthal 1) There are no jobs for new graduates, and starting your own firm is incredibly difficult, as I can attest to. 2) What you study in law school will have zero bearing on what law practice actually looks like in the real world. 3) Any statistic that makes salary or employment prospects look good is misleading (i.e. NALP statistics for salary may indicate a median salary of $125,000, but in reality it is a bimodal distribution, and your more realistic salary is more like $50,000, if you're lucky. Similarly, see every law school \"employment after graduation\" statistic ever, when you factor for the fact that law schools literally count Starbucks baristas as being employed, and offer in-house temp jobs to pad their numbers).",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:43:13.892Z"),
    "question" : "What are some facts I should know before studying to be a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7f3ab30e99eeabcd43fd"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/My-lawyer-daughter-hired-a-lawyer-who-is-giving-her-very-dangerous-legal-advice-that-will-end-her-career-so-how-do-I-stop-this-crazy-attorney?-",
    "answer" : "Jennifer Ellis Your daughter is a lawyer working with a lawyer. You think the lawyer is giving her dangerous legal advice. Since your daughter is a lawyer, she should be in a position to understand whether the lawyer’s advice is appropriate or not. She was smart enough to understand when she needed counsel, after all. Why do you think the advice is dangerous? If you have a legal basis to believe this, and can make an appropriate legal argument, you should talk to your daughter about the situation. You should be able to sit down with your daughter and explain your concerns in a calm and appropriate fashion. You should be able to do so using the law itself. You can also ask your daughter to get a second opinion. If money is a concern, you can offer to pay for it. Understand though, that the lawyer will work Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:44:26.429Z"),
    "question" : "My lawyer daughter hired a lawyer who is giving her very dangerous legal advice that will end her career so how do I stop this crazy attorney? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7f73b30e99eeabcd440b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-is-practising-law-stressful?-",
    "answer" : "Suzanne Kiera Anthony I practiced business litigation representing major financial institutions and corporations mostly in fraud cases where big money and, often, people’s professional careers were in issue. On average, I handled 35-40 cases at any given time for 5 clients. Some cases involved only two sides, but many involved several. Every side had its lawyer(s). Litigation includes abundant correspondence, telephone conversations with clients and opposing attorneys, often massive written discovery and depositions on all sides, witnesses to prepare, sometimes expert witnesses, many law and motion matters requiring research and preparation of briefs, replies and oral argument, lots of hearings, settlement conferences, mediations and occasionally trial. Every client thinks they deserve your undivided attention. Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:45:23.242Z"),
    "question" : "Why is practising law stressful? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7f83b30e99eeabcd440f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Does-an-engineer-earn-more-money-or-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "I agree with the previous answer. Being a lawyer is very competitive and I know a lot of lawyers who are out of work and have had to find another career. On the other hand, if you’re successful in law, you can make a lot of money; but in order to do that, you have to be very aggressive and maybe even do some things that might be considered distasteful (have you heard the term “ambulance chaser”?) A software engineer is less likely to be out of work (as a lawyer might be) and is much more likely to have a good dependable income with some upside potential. Those two careers have radically different personalities associated with them to be successful. You should base your choice on which profession best matches your personality. If you choose one that doesn’t match your personality, you’re not  Continue Reading I agree with the previous answer. Being a lawyer is very competitive and I know a lot of lawyers who are out of work and have had to find another career. On the other hand, if you’re successful in law, you can make a lot of money; but in order to do that, you have to be very aggressive and maybe even do some things that might be considered distasteful (have you heard the term “ambulance chaser”?) A software engineer is less likely to be out of work (as a lawyer might be) and is much more likely to have a good dependable income with some upside potential. Those two careers have radically different personalities associated with them to be successful. You should base your choice on which profession best matches your personality. If you choose one that doesn’t match your personality, you’re not  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:45:39.934Z"),
    "question" : "Does an engineer earn more money or a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7f94b30e99eeabcd4419"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-criminal-lawyers-choose-between-prosecutor-and-public-defender-for-their-career?-",
    "answer" : "John Christopher First, I'm going to lump together the whole of the public defense bar, i.e., the various types of public defenders (salaried employees of the state or some agency) and assigned/panel defenders (who, essentially, work on contract). Sometimes, it isn't always a choice. For example, appointed/panel work often is, unfortunately, a place where attorneys \"end up,\" especially places without a vigorous defense bar. See Better Call Saul for what that work can be like. And hiring at prosecutor's offices is probably often more competitive (or snobbish) than a defender's office. (That doesn't mean PD work is always second-choice or less than first-rate, however: I know many PDs who turned down Big Law for public service.) You also get a fair amount of Manichaeans: The avenging-angel types who think \"we' Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:45:56.416Z"),
    "question" : "How do criminal lawyers choose between prosecutor and public defender for their career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c7fd6b30e99eeabcd4428"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-would-a-lawyer-do-if-this-was-not-a-profitable-career?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What would a lawyer do if this was not a profitable career?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:47:02.079Z"),
    "question" : "What would a lawyer do if this was not a profitable career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8020b30e99eeabcd443b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-does-the-career-of-freshly-minted-Ivy-League-lawyers-interested-in-criminal-law-differ-from-their-peers?-",
    "answer" : "No matter what facet of law you choose and where you attend law school, you’re going to start at the bottom at your first job. This is because law school graduates—smart though they may be—have little in the way of practical skills and need time, often many years, to turn into good working lawyers. Regardless of your LSAT score and GPA, no employer is going to “turn loose” someone who’s never really done the work of being a lawyer. The main difference between attending an elite law school and a less-highly-regarded one is where you have the chance to start your career. There are some jobs—positions with the federal government, positions at the best law firms—that are reserved only for graduates of the nation’s best law schools and the occasional valedictorian/near-valedictorian from elsewhe Continue Reading No matter what facet of law you choose and where you attend law school, you’re going to start at the bottom at your first job. This is because law school graduates—smart though they may be—have little in the way of practical skills and need time, often many years, to turn into good working lawyers. Regardless of your LSAT score and GPA, no employer is going to “turn loose” someone who’s never really done the work of being a lawyer. The main difference between attending an elite law school and a less-highly-regarded one is where you have the chance to start your career. There are some jobs—positions with the federal government, positions at the best law firms—that are reserved only for graduates of the nation’s best law schools and the occasional valedictorian/near-valedictorian from elsewhe Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:48:16.425Z"),
    "question" : "How does the career of freshly minted Ivy League lawyers interested in criminal law differ from their peers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8037b30e99eeabcd4441"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-being-an-environmental-lawyer-a-good-career?-",
    "answer" : "Having worked in the local government and environmental and conservation fields all my life and having a reasonable acquaintanceship with environmental law - have taught and published in the field (I am not a lawyer), I can say with reasonable sincerity that the field is important, but often necessary because of screw-ups in other areas of life and generally bad practices. The field can be prone to negativity and it depends on who your clients are. We do need environmental lawyers, but I always suggest that people also chose other complementary areas of law as well to provide a more balanced practice. Some combinations like trade and environmental law go together, as does customary and treaty law and environmental law. It also helps to learn something of the language of the disciplines you w Continue Reading Having worked in the local government and environmental and conservation fields all my life and having a reasonable acquaintanceship with environmental law - have taught and published in the field (I am not a lawyer), I can say with reasonable sincerity that the field is important, but often necessary because of screw-ups in other areas of life and generally bad practices. The field can be prone to negativity and it depends on who your clients are. We do need environmental lawyers, but I always suggest that people also chose other complementary areas of law as well to provide a more balanced practice. Some combinations like trade and environmental law go together, as does customary and treaty law and environmental law. It also helps to learn something of the language of the disciplines you w Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:48:39.120Z"),
    "question" : "Is being an environmental lawyer a good career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8046b30e99eeabcd4447"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-an-LLB-degree-from-India-useful-if-I-want-my-career-as-a-corporate-lawyer-outside-India?-",
    "answer" : "Amy Jones, Legal Advisor at Ahlawat & Associates Advocates (2012-present)Answered 1 year ago · Author has 217 answers and 207.7K answer viewsHow much do corporate lawyers earn on an average in India? Can I become a corporate lawyer abroad if I study law from India? Amy Jones Salary of fresher corporate lawyers is affected a lot by the kind of institution they passed out from. Anyone graduating from a top-level NLU can easily get Rs 12-15 lakhs per annum as a beginner. People with mid-level experience can about 25-30 lakhs every year. Anyone who passes out from mid-level NLU can get offers of Rs 7-10 lakhs. People who specialize in an area which does not have many experts like the insolvency law in India can expect to get even more. For professionals who become partners in their firms, the sky is the limit. Now coming to the second part of your question, yes you can work as a corporate lawyer abroad even if you pass from an Indian institution. You will have to fulfill the criteria for working as an attorney like completing a valid law degree from a recognized in Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:48:54.287Z"),
    "question" : "Is an LLB degree from India useful if I want my career as a corporate lawyer outside India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c807bb30e99eeabcd4455"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-possible-for-a-lawyer-to-have-never-lost-a-case-in-their-entire-career?-",
    "answer" : "“Is it possible for a lawyer to have never lost a case in their entire career?” Yes. There are many, many attorneys who have been practicing law for decades and have never lost a case. We call these people “transactional lawyers.” The easiest way to become a lawyer who has never lost a case is by specializing in a practice area that does not include litigation. Some other kinds lawyers who have never lost a case in their entire career might include: Brand-new lawyers who have only been practicing for a week.Lawyers who cherry-pick the cases they accept, and only take the slam dunks.More importantly, though, we need to define the terms “win” and “lose” as most lawyers view them. I’m going to steal the first sentence of J. Brian Watkins’ separate answer: “What is a loss?” Any attorney who has th Continue Reading “Is it possible for a lawyer to have never lost a case in their entire career?” Yes. There are many, many attorneys who have been practicing law for decades and have never lost a case. We call these people “transactional lawyers.” The easiest way to become a lawyer who has never lost a case is by specializing in a practice area that does not include litigation. Some other kinds lawyers who have never lost a case in their entire career might include: Brand-new lawyers who have only been practicing for a week.Lawyers who cherry-pick the cases they accept, and only take the slam dunks.More importantly, though, we need to define the terms “win” and “lose” as most lawyers view them. I’m going to steal the first sentence of J. Brian Watkins’ separate answer: “What is a loss?” Any attorney who has th Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:49:47.167Z"),
    "question" : "Is it possible for a lawyer to have never lost a case in their entire career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c808ab30e99eeabcd4459"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-high-school-classes-should-I-take-if-I-want-to-be-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "Alice Baker In high school, take all of the college prep classes that you can get — Math, Science, English, Social Studies, Foreign Language. Don’t neglect math and science. In college, major in whatever you like. There is no particular course of undergraduate study that you need to take. Don’t worry about taking anything that your college labels as a “pre-law” class; you’ll learn everything you need to know once you get to law school. Instead, focus on learning things that you will need to know as an attorney, and that law schools don’t teach. Take math. You need to have enough math to understand interest rates, basic statistics, and how to calculate the present value of an income stream over time.Take economics. You need to know the theory underlying interest rates and other financial issues. Many peoContinue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:50:02.214Z"),
    "question" : "What high school classes should I take if I want to be a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c80ceb30e99eeabcd446d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-prepare-my-9-year-old-for-a-career-as-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "I don't understand why YOU would choose a profession for your child at any age. As your child grows up they may want to do something altogether different. Are you going to smother their desire to be who they want to be? Are you going to choose for your child a profession that they may hate and be unhappy working at? Are you a controlling person that makes a decision for your child as to what he should be as an adult? Right now at 9 years old he should be allowed to be a child and not pushed to select a career that YOU choose. Don't prepare your child for a profession, instead prepare your child to be honest, loving, loyal, have self-confidence, be open minded to new ideas, to do well in school, college if the choose to go to college. Most of all encourage your child to make his own decisions,  Continue Reading I don't understand why YOU would choose a profession for your child at any age. As your child grows up they may want to do something altogether different. Are you going to smother their desire to be who they want to be? Are you going to choose for your child a profession that they may hate and be unhappy working at? Are you a controlling person that makes a decision for your child as to what he should be as an adult? Right now at 9 years old he should be allowed to be a child and not pushed to select a career that YOU choose. Don't prepare your child for a profession, instead prepare your child to be honest, loving, loyal, have self-confidence, be open minded to new ideas, to do well in school, college if the choose to go to college. Most of all encourage your child to make his own decisions,  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:51:10.770Z"),
    "question" : "How can I prepare my 9 year old for a career as a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c80eeb30e99eeabcd4475"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-most-important-law-school-classes-to-take-to-prepare-for-a-career-as-a-transactional-lawyer-representing-startups-and-VC-firms?-",
    "answer" : "At some schools there is a capstone class that ties the various strings together in a more practical manner. For example, I teach a class at USF Law called Startups & Venture Capital (I have also seen this class called Corporate Transactions or Business Transactions at other schools). In that class we follow a hypothetical company through various transactions: incorporation, joint tech venture, investment transaction, and discuss a bit about M&A, IPOs and other transactions. We tie together corporate, tax, securities and IP law into practical assignments, such as drafting a term sheet, a restricted stock purchase agreement, and an LLC operating agreement. The goal is to synthesize the theory into practical advice to a client. I can't recommend a class like that enough. Startup and venture c Continue Reading At some schools there is a capstone class that ties the various strings together in a more practical manner. For example, I teach a class at USF Law called Startups & Venture Capital (I have also seen this class called Corporate Transactions or Business Transactions at other schools). In that class we follow a hypothetical company through various transactions: incorporation, joint tech venture, investment transaction, and discuss a bit about M&A, IPOs and other transactions. We tie together corporate, tax, securities and IP law into practical assignments, such as drafting a term sheet, a restricted stock purchase agreement, and an LLC operating agreement. The goal is to synthesize the theory into practical advice to a client. I can't recommend a class like that enough. Startup and venture c Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:51:42.850Z"),
    "question" : "What are the most important law school classes to take to prepare for a career as a transactional lawyer representing startups and VC firms? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8101b30e99eeabcd447b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-typical-career-pathway-for-an-aspiring-IP-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "Depends on whether you will work for a firm or you will be an \"in house\" attorney (working for the legal dept. of a corporation). In a firm, you start as an Associate and then after a few years the partners decide whether to make you a Partner or not.If you don't make it, you either leave (most common) or remain as Senior Associate or Counsel.If you make it, later on, you may become a Senior Partner, or a \"Named Partner,\"(very rare) it all depends on the size of the firm. In house attorneys have a traditional corporate ladder; such as, counsel, senior counsel, director, Sr. director, vice president, Sr.  VP, Chief Legal Counsel, etc. (the titles may vary, but you get the idea). It is not unusual to start in a firm and then move on as an in-house attorney. The other way is still possible, bu Continue Reading Depends on whether you will work for a firm or you will be an \"in house\" attorney (working for the legal dept. of a corporation). In a firm, you start as an Associate and then after a few years the partners decide whether to make you a Partner or not.If you don't make it, you either leave (most common) or remain as Senior Associate or Counsel.If you make it, later on, you may become a Senior Partner, or a \"Named Partner,\"(very rare) it all depends on the size of the firm. In house attorneys have a traditional corporate ladder; such as, counsel, senior counsel, director, Sr. director, vice president, Sr.  VP, Chief Legal Counsel, etc. (the titles may vary, but you get the idea). It is not unusual to start in a firm and then move on as an in-house attorney. The other way is still possible, bu Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:52:01.889Z"),
    "question" : "What is the typical career pathway for an aspiring IP lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8127b30e99eeabcd4485"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-try-to-pursue-a-career-as-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "A law degree is not worth it if you are only interested in the rumored high income. Relatively high incomes are possible in the practice of law but they come at a great cost, long, long hours, angst, worry, heartache, tedium and absolutely no assurance that your degree will land you any job let alone a high paying one. I know many people in relatively blue collar fields who outearn even my highest paid colleagues. The point is Law is a calling not a job. If you are only in it for the money you will be among the 50% of law grads who leave the porfession within the first 5 years. If, on the other hand, you have a passion for debate, continuous learning and study, love language and the minutiae of drafting contracts or helping those in need of advocacy, it is worth it; but not for the dough.  Continue Reading A law degree is not worth it if you are only interested in the rumored high income. Relatively high incomes are possible in the practice of law but they come at a great cost, long, long hours, angst, worry, heartache, tedium and absolutely no assurance that your degree will land you any job let alone a high paying one. I know many people in relatively blue collar fields who outearn even my highest paid colleagues. The point is Law is a calling not a job. If you are only in it for the money you will be among the 50% of law grads who leave the porfession within the first 5 years. If, on the other hand, you have a passion for debate, continuous learning and study, love language and the minutiae of drafting contracts or helping those in need of advocacy, it is worth it; but not for the dough.  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:52:39.031Z"),
    "question" : "Should I try to pursue a career as a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8148b30e99eeabcd448d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-universities-guarantee-you-a-career-as-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "None. No college or university, even the big-name famous ones (think Harvard), will ever “guarantee” you or any other student anything. There are no guarantees in life. Universities aren’t responsible for getting you a job in anything (lawyer, engineer, doctor, accountant, nurse, pick any profession). If your chosen future profession requires a college degree (meaning a bachelor’s degree) in order to work in that field, then you go to college, find a major that will help you realize your goal, graduate from college with a respectable GPA. That still is no guarantee that you’ll be hired. The next steps are on YOU—it is up to you to do internships (if required), to make use of your school’s career services, to learn how to network, and more and hope that you’ll be hired. As for a career as a l Continue Reading None. No college or university, even the big-name famous ones (think Harvard), will ever “guarantee” you or any other student anything. There are no guarantees in life. Universities aren’t responsible for getting you a job in anything (lawyer, engineer, doctor, accountant, nurse, pick any profession). If your chosen future profession requires a college degree (meaning a bachelor’s degree) in order to work in that field, then you go to college, find a major that will help you realize your goal, graduate from college with a respectable GPA. That still is no guarantee that you’ll be hired. The next steps are on YOU—it is up to you to do internships (if required), to make use of your school’s career services, to learn how to network, and more and hope that you’ll be hired. As for a career as a l Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:53:12.117Z"),
    "question" : "Which universities guarantee you a career as a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8167b30e99eeabcd4496"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Where-can-I-find-a-job-as-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "Erik Sapp There is no way to answer that as what people find interesting is different. I went to law school to practice criminal law. I wanted to get in the courtroom. I wanted to have variety in my caseload. My former boss was an immigration attorney. He loved immigration. (He was himself an immigrant.) He loved getting into the details of immigration law. He disliked actually going to court. He had been practicing immigration law for over 20 years, so clearly he found it interesting. He took almost no criminal cases and the ones he did take were mostly from existing clients. Which of us is “right?” Obviously, we both are, as we are doing work we find interesting. The fact that I did not enjoy his work does not mean it was not interesting to someone who like it (like him). Allen Inks",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:53:43.881Z"),
    "question" : "Where can I find a job as a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c81aeb30e99eeabcd44a8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-a-better-career-option-for-a-corporate-lawyer-from-a-reputed-NLU-or-IIM-Indore-in-the-IPM-programme?-",
    "answer" : "Anusha Soni, AIR 36, AILET 2016,  Student - IPM batch of 2016-21Updated 3 years ago · Upvoted by Navya Singhal, studied at Integrated Programme in Management, IIM Indore (2021) and Sarvesh Pachgade, studied Integrated Programme in Management, IIM Indore at Indian Institute of Management Indore (2021)Which is a better career option for a corporate lawyer from a reputed NLU or IIM Indore in the IPM programme? Anusha Soni Sarvesh Pachgade",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:54:54.417Z"),
    "question" : "Which is a better career option for a corporate lawyer from a reputed NLU or IIM Indore in the IPM programme? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8225b30e99eeabcd44ca"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Do-nurses-change-careers-to-lawyers?-",
    "answer" : "IN MOST CASES NOWADAYS it’s a REALLY bad idea to go to law school, because the field is SO overloaded. HOWEVER, there are exceptions. Those involve “dual specialties”, where the person must have qualifications in two fields. Those are generally limited to the following: Law plus accountingLaw plus an MBA plus a track record of successful managementLaw plus undergrad physical sciences degree, e.g., chemistry, physics — go into patent lawLaw plus engineering - go into patent lawLaw plus medicine.You would have to go to law school, take the bar exam, etc., just like anyone else. Generally, anyone with a degree in science, engineering, or medicine can ace law school, because those majors are a lot harder than the typical undergrad liberal arts topics. If you do go to law school, you should seriou Continue Reading IN MOST CASES NOWADAYS it’s a REALLY bad idea to go to law school, because the field is SO overloaded. HOWEVER, there are exceptions. Those involve “dual specialties”, where the person must have qualifications in two fields. Those are generally limited to the following: Law plus accountingLaw plus an MBA plus a track record of successful managementLaw plus undergrad physical sciences degree, e.g., chemistry, physics — go into patent lawLaw plus engineering - go into patent lawLaw plus medicine.You would have to go to law school, take the bar exam, etc., just like anyone else. Generally, anyone with a degree in science, engineering, or medicine can ace law school, because those majors are a lot harder than the typical undergrad liberal arts topics. If you do go to law school, you should seriou Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:56:53.592Z"),
    "question" : "Do nurses change careers to lawyers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c826fb30e99eeabcd44da"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-top-books-to-read-before-starting-a-career-as-a-criminal-defence-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "Josephanie Franco Here are my opinions: Black’s Law Dictionary, although it does not have a means to tell you the proper way to spell, “defense.”Gerry Spence’s book, “How To Argue And Win Every Time”. It’s a fantastic read, once when I was sitting in the courtroom’s anteroom reading it between cases, opposing counsel saw me with the book and shrieked, “No! No! No! You have to give me a chance!!!” and ripped the book out of my hands and took off. I never saw my book again, despite me asking for it back ☹️;“Getting To Yes”. It’s a great book on negotiation and compromise skills. The best legal work is done outside of trial. Trial happens when you cannot come to an agreement on how to resolve charges. Going into trial can be a crap shoot, and is long and tedious. If one cannot negotiate a good settlement, it’s Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T05:58:07.389Z"),
    "question" : "What are the top books to read before starting a career as a criminal defence lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c82eeb30e99eeabcd44f6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-career-as-a-tax-lawyer-rewarding?-",
    "answer" : "For me it was. Not only financially but also in clients that became friends. However the tax season is pretty much only two months so it would be wise to combine it with a payroll service or bookkeeping or both. I didn’t because I had four other businesses so the tax business was just a sideline. I only had 200 clients and did all the taxes myself. With a good tax program, and a prepared client, a tax return only takes about 20 minutes.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:00:14.627Z"),
    "question" : "Is a career as a tax lawyer rewarding? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c832fb30e99eeabcd4508"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-second-career-options-for-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "Lee Ballentine, Futurist, former recruiter, six time Top Writer on Quora.Answered 4 years ago · Author has 12.6K answers and 37.9M answer viewsWhat are some good second career options for a lawyer? Lee Ballentine There are lots of options. I have a lot of lawyer friends who have created second careers for themselves in related fields, often simply because they were burned out from the incredibly long workdays and weeks of working in law firms. Here are some ideas. Lobbying. If you enjoy the legislative process, lobbying, especially at the state level, can be a fun and interesting career. Start by talking to lobbyists. You may even find a more senior person looking to share work with a younger associate.Corporate boards/advisor. Especially for smaller companies. I’m talking about everything to do with boards, including sitting on them. There may be opportunities to do some low-key legal work as well, even trading for some equity. Or board development—helping companies recruit and get the most out of Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:01:19.229Z"),
    "question" : "What are some good second career options for a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c837cb30e99eeabcd451c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-career-between-a-lawyer-and-an-IAS?-",
    "answer" : "hey, This is an interesting question..Everyone will have to face similar situation once in a lifetime.See,I will personally suggest that you should choose career based on your interest and importantly your skill..If you are a brilliant lawyer but lacks interest in civil service,IAS will be a boredom for you after many year. But if you really like social service and you are ready to put in your best IAS is for you man..But people should be your priority,,and respect and pride comes with job>>> ALL the best The Unknown",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:02:36.362Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best career between a lawyer and an IAS? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c838cb30e99eeabcd4520"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Do-lawyers-have-to-choose-defense-or-prosecutor-for-their-whole-career?-",
    "answer" : "Once you pass the bar, and sometimes a little before, some job seekers are hired by the state to become prosecutors. Others end up in a general mix, either on their own, or maybe as a member of a firm. Large, or small. Those that become prosecutors are generally not involved in other areas of the law. Later in their career, they can remain in the criminal field as a prosecutor, arising to major cases, or maybe the chief’s desk. As an alternative, they can jump ship and become defense counsel. They are still pretty much specialized in the criminal system, but if he/she is fortunate enough to get into a general practice firm that has hired him /her for his/her criminal experience to do defense work, he/she will probable also be required to do some general law and he/she will get the experienc Continue Reading Once you pass the bar, and sometimes a little before, some job seekers are hired by the state to become prosecutors. Others end up in a general mix, either on their own, or maybe as a member of a firm. Large, or small. Those that become prosecutors are generally not involved in other areas of the law. Later in their career, they can remain in the criminal field as a prosecutor, arising to major cases, or maybe the chief’s desk. As an alternative, they can jump ship and become defense counsel. They are still pretty much specialized in the criminal system, but if he/she is fortunate enough to get into a general practice firm that has hired him /her for his/her criminal experience to do defense work, he/she will probable also be required to do some general law and he/she will get the experienc Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:02:52.770Z"),
    "question" : "Do lawyers have to choose defense or prosecutor for their whole career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c83b5b30e99eeabcd452b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-career-opportunity-for-lawyers-in-india?-",
    "answer" : "The legal sector has always been one of the most respected and acknowledged fields in India. While people think that law does not offer a very expansive career choice, it is quite the opposite. Lawyers, judges, legal advisors & consultants are among the most recognized legal roles in society.  Career Options in Law Judge As a judge, you’d be responsible for presiding over court proceedings. You’d have to listen to the arguments of both sides and give the final verdict after analysing the case and the evidence presented before you. To become a judge in India, you’d have to crack the state-level examination for judiciary services (PCS J). You must have a bachelor’s in law (LLB) to be eligible for this exam. Every state has different eligibility requirements for this exam, so keep that in mind wh Continue Reading The legal sector has always been one of the most respected and acknowledged fields in India. While people think that law does not offer a very expansive career choice, it is quite the opposite. Lawyers, judges, legal advisors & consultants are among the most recognized legal roles in society.  Career Options in Law Judge As a judge, you’d be responsible for presiding over court proceedings. You’d have to listen to the arguments of both sides and give the final verdict after analysing the case and the evidence presented before you. To become a judge in India, you’d have to crack the state-level examination for judiciary services (PCS J). You must have a bachelor’s in law (LLB) to be eligible for this exam. Every state has different eligibility requirements for this exam, so keep that in mind wh Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:03:33.776Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best career opportunity for lawyers in india? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8408b30e99eeabcd453d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-can-I-do-at-age-15-if-I-want-to-become-a-great-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "Ricky Anand The basic Law degree (LL B) is a 3-year course's However, another option is to pursue an integrated honours degree offered by autonomous law schools, which takes 5 years to complete. E.g.: B.A., LL.B. (Honors); B.B.A, LL.B. (Honors) etc. The options available for specialisation are Constitutional law, Business law, International Trade law, Crime and criminology, International law, Law & Agriculture and Intellectual Property law. Cost: Tuition fees: Ranges from INR50, 000 – INR90, 000 Eligibility: Bachelor’s degree in law (LL.B) can be pursued in India only after completing an under graduation degree in any field, such as http://B.Com, B. Sc etc. or choosing to pursue an integrated honours degree. The minimum age to enrol in an LL.B course is 20 years and the maximum age is 30 years. If a student choo Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:04:56.045Z"),
    "question" : "What can I do at age 15 if I want to become a great lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c843eb30e99eeabcd454e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-fork-in-the-road-that-leads-some-lawyers-to-become-high-powered-trial-attorneys-and-others-to-become-career-public-defenders?-",
    "answer" : "Lawyering in reality is nothing like the media portrays. It is difficult, nasty and often unrewarding. It takes years to build competency and clients. Often your career is made or broken depending upon the lawyers with whom you were surrounded when you began practice. Young lawyers have absolutely no idea what they are in for. Many, like myself, found themselves having graduated but with no real desire to work in their undergraduate field of study. What young lawyers do understand is competition. The law is, after all, merely a set of rules for conflict—i.e. legalized and formalized war. There are lawyers who strategize and consult, but in reality, the law exists solely to make (or coerce or persuade—use the euphemism of your choice) someone do something they would otherwise be disinclined t Continue Reading Lawyering in reality is nothing like the media portrays. It is difficult, nasty and often unrewarding. It takes years to build competency and clients. Often your career is made or broken depending upon the lawyers with whom you were surrounded when you began practice. Young lawyers have absolutely no idea what they are in for. Many, like myself, found themselves having graduated but with no real desire to work in their undergraduate field of study. What young lawyers do understand is competition. The law is, after all, merely a set of rules for conflict—i.e. legalized and formalized war. There are lawyers who strategize and consult, but in reality, the law exists solely to make (or coerce or persuade—use the euphemism of your choice) someone do something they would otherwise be disinclined t Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:05:50.734Z"),
    "question" : "What is the fork in the road that leads some lawyers to become high powered trial attorneys and others to become career public defenders? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8457b30e99eeabcd4555"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-build-a-successful-career-as-a-corporate-lawyer-in-Singapore?-",
    "answer" : "Nishi Sharma",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:06:15.687Z"),
    "question" : "How do I build a successful career as a corporate lawyer in Singapore? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c84edb30e99eeabcd457b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-possible-for-a-lawyer-to-appear-in-court-less-than-5-times-throughout-his-career?-",
    "answer" : "More than possible — it’s likely. Litigation is only one legal specialty, though it is a very large one. But there are many more lawyers who specialize in other things — intellectual property, labor & employment, taxes, will and trusts, corporate governance, mergers & acquisitions, antitrust, finance, and so on. In most of those areas, litigation occasionally arises, either from a government action or from a suit. But that doesn’t mean those attorneys with other specialties will then litigate the case; nearly always, what they do is consult with a litigation specialist (within the same organization, or hired for that particular case) to handle it. Also, even a litigation matter doesn’t necessarily end up in court — most cases are settled out of court, and good litigators are skilled at those Continue Reading More than possible — it’s likely. Litigation is only one legal specialty, though it is a very large one. But there are many more lawyers who specialize in other things — intellectual property, labor & employment, taxes, will and trusts, corporate governance, mergers & acquisitions, antitrust, finance, and so on. In most of those areas, litigation occasionally arises, either from a government action or from a suit. But that doesn’t mean those attorneys with other specialties will then litigate the case; nearly always, what they do is consult with a litigation specialist (within the same organization, or hired for that particular case) to handle it. Also, even a litigation matter doesn’t necessarily end up in court — most cases are settled out of court, and good litigators are skilled at those Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:08:45.683Z"),
    "question" : "Is it possible for a lawyer to appear in court less than 5 times throughout his career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8533b30e99eeabcd458b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-much-do-lawyers-earn-in-Pakistan-at-the-start-of-their-career?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:09:55.137Z"),
    "question" : "How much do lawyers earn in Pakistan at the start of their career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c85a3b30e99eeabcd45a9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-many-Sati-practices-have-you-seen-in-your-whole-career-as-a-lawyer-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Literally none!! Not a lawyer BTW Sati was banned in 1829 With the help of many reformers like Raja Ram Mohan Roy . For those who do not know, Sati means a widow commiting suicide by throwing herself in husband's burning pyre. It was seen in rise after the 10th century during Islamic invasions of India in mostly the sikh & Rajput families where Muslim Kings & their armies would kill men, enslave children(The word “Bacha” actually means child slave) & take women as Sexual slaves & forcefully convert them. In order to save their Honor women would burn themselves in a pyre as soon as their militaries lost the war check:- Jauhar Rajput Queens With 1,000 years of invasions​ this gradually became a tradition & as soon as the Mughal (Muslim) rule ended, soon enough this practice was abolished. Unlike  Continue Reading Literally none!! Not a lawyer BTW Sati was banned in 1829 With the help of many reformers like Raja Ram Mohan Roy . For those who do not know, Sati means a widow commiting suicide by throwing herself in husband's burning pyre. It was seen in rise after the 10th century during Islamic invasions of India in mostly the sikh & Rajput families where Muslim Kings & their armies would kill men, enslave children(The word “Bacha” actually means child slave) & take women as Sexual slaves & forcefully convert them. In order to save their Honor women would burn themselves in a pyre as soon as their militaries lost the war check:- Jauhar Rajput Queens With 1,000 years of invasions​ this gradually became a tradition & as soon as the Mughal (Muslim) rule ended, soon enough this practice was abolished. Unlike  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:11:47.658Z"),
    "question" : "How many Sati practices have you seen in your whole career as a lawyer in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8672b30e99eeabcd45db"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-after-becoming-a-lawyer-at-40-years-of-age-in-india?-",
    "answer" : "Lawyer mean practicing lawyer or just a fresh graduate who would now go under training under lawyers? Whatever it is, if you have the energy and the wit, no one can stop you. In fact your age can be an advantage as many people do not like to go with young lawyers. Leeban Arivalazhan",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:15:14.817Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career after becoming a lawyer at 40 years of age in india? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8682b30e99eeabcd45df"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-career-as-a-legal-adviser-or-a-corporate-lawyer-better-than-litigation-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "In the early years, a lawyer who proposes to build her career in litigation faces huge challenges, when compared to a lawyer working in a corporate law firm or who works as an in-house Counsel of a company. While her counterparts in the law firm or company enjoy a steady income, a litigation Lawyer has to slog a as a junior often without remuneration for a few years, learning the art of advocacy. Once established, litigation lawyers have the opportunity to earn well but so do the ones in coprporate Law firms and companies whose Income and perks steadily rise as they grow to be seniors and Partners. However litigation lawyers have the satisfaction of actually matching their wits with that of their opponent and convincing judges to decide in their favour. To stand up and argue and demolish wh Continue Reading In the early years, a lawyer who proposes to build her career in litigation faces huge challenges, when compared to a lawyer working in a corporate law firm or who works as an in-house Counsel of a company. While her counterparts in the law firm or company enjoy a steady income, a litigation Lawyer has to slog a as a junior often without remuneration for a few years, learning the art of advocacy. Once established, litigation lawyers have the opportunity to earn well but so do the ones in coprporate Law firms and companies whose Income and perks steadily rise as they grow to be seniors and Partners. However litigation lawyers have the satisfaction of actually matching their wits with that of their opponent and convincing judges to decide in their favour. To stand up and argue and demolish wh Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:15:30.301Z"),
    "question" : "Is a career as a legal adviser or a corporate lawyer better than litigation in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c875db30e99eeabcd4613"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-careers-require-the-most-education-beside-doctors-and-lawyers?-",
    "answer" : "Michael Depietro  Pilots, need to know ins and outs of every situation possible and they may/may not encounter it in future. An experienced pilot with say with even 15 years of experience can also be erratic at times(as it is human nature) and scope of error determines the distance between Life and Death of hundreds, they need to study regularly which can be for change in procedures or changing to a new aircraft. Knowledge is the mantra for it and hence pilots study a lot they have no other option. Hence every pilot has to know everything.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:19:09.281Z"),
    "question" : "What careers require the most education beside doctors and lawyers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8796b30e99eeabcd4620"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Would-any-lawyer-defending-Trump-at-his-impeachment-trial-be-taken-seriously-for-the-rest-of-their-career?-",
    "answer" : "You do understand the justice system of the free world ? Everyone is entitled to have an advocate to represent them in any court . That person whether it be Johnny Corcoran , Robert Kardashian or Rudy Guiliani etc . The justice system fortunately presumes innocence until proven guilty. Trial by media on the other hand is far more cruel and moronic. It’s just a Kangaroo court . On your opinion Trump should be swinging from a tree to satisfy you and your bloodlust mob . You are why these people who marched on and invaded the Capital building. Because two wrongs certainly don’t make a right. Ever since Donald Trump ( certainly no Saint ) was elected as President, he has been mocked and denounced by anyone from the left of society. 75 million Americans and many in the free world happen to beli Continue Reading You do understand the justice system of the free world ? Everyone is entitled to have an advocate to represent them in any court . That person whether it be Johnny Corcoran , Robert Kardashian or Rudy Guiliani etc . The justice system fortunately presumes innocence until proven guilty. Trial by media on the other hand is far more cruel and moronic. It’s just a Kangaroo court . On your opinion Trump should be swinging from a tree to satisfy you and your bloodlust mob . You are why these people who marched on and invaded the Capital building. Because two wrongs certainly don’t make a right. Ever since Donald Trump ( certainly no Saint ) was elected as President, he has been mocked and denounced by anyone from the left of society. 75 million Americans and many in the free world happen to beli Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:20:06.090Z"),
    "question" : "Would any lawyer defending Trump at his impeachment trial be taken seriously for the rest of their career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c87cbb30e99eeabcd4630"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Was-Hilary-Clinton-ever-brought-up-on-charges-or-investigated-during-her-career-as-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "Dana H. Shultz  Its Hillary folks…she has been involved in lots of dirty scandals Whitewater, explained for people who don't remember the Clinton presidency But as any loving Democrat will tell you , she has never been convicted of anything",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:20:59.925Z"),
    "question" : "Was Hilary Clinton ever brought up on charges or investigated during her career as a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c87feb30e99eeabcd463c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Are-you-doing-very-well-today-as-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "Really, really, well! After 43 years of practice, I retired and am happily on a second career as the author of The Toki-Girl and the Sparrow-Boy series in which magical realism and historical fantasy collide in Meiji Era Japan! Scott Grundy",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:21:50.258Z"),
    "question" : "Are you doing very well today as a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8863b30e99eeabcd4654"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-lawyers-advance-in-their-careers?-",
    "answer" : "Not by winning cases in court like Perry Mason. They make all their money with that 33.3% they get from settlements. They love settlements. They go to sleep at night dreaming about them.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:23:31.303Z"),
    "question" : "How do lawyers advance in their careers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8887b30e99eeabcd465e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-non-legal-career-opportunities-for-a-corporate-startup-lawyer-who-wants-to-leave-the-practice-of-law?-",
    "answer" : "Interested in moving or working with a UK-based legal tech startup? Linkilaw has been founded about 18 months ago and our mission is to democratise the legal industry by making it more accessible and less intimidating. We’re always looking for great legal minds to help us innovate further. Shoot me an email if you’re interested! Alexandra@linkilaw.com 10",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:24:07.751Z"),
    "question" : "What are some good non-legal career opportunities for a corporate startup lawyer who wants to leave the practice of law? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8903b30e99eeabcd467c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-important-is-networking-for-career-success-as-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "Extremely important! If you’re at a really high end competitive law school, it helps you meet upper classmen and women who can tell you what you actually need to study to do well.It helps you find a job if you’re in law school or just graduated.It helps you find potential sources for new business.It helps you meet and form relationships with lawyers who you can refer cases to that aren’t in your niche or that you would like help with.It helps you form relationships with lawyers who you can call up and brainstorm with if you need a sounding board.If helps you find a more experienced attorney who can mentor you over lunch or on the phone, free of office politics, or when lawyers at your office are preoccupied.The list goes on. Believe it or not I met my wife at a local young lawyer’s bar asso Continue Reading Extremely important! If you’re at a really high end competitive law school, it helps you meet upper classmen and women who can tell you what you actually need to study to do well.It helps you find a job if you’re in law school or just graduated.It helps you find potential sources for new business.It helps you meet and form relationships with lawyers who you can refer cases to that aren’t in your niche or that you would like help with.It helps you form relationships with lawyers who you can call up and brainstorm with if you need a sounding board.If helps you find a more experienced attorney who can mentor you over lunch or on the phone, free of office politics, or when lawyers at your office are preoccupied.The list goes on. Believe it or not I met my wife at a local young lawyer’s bar asso Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:26:11.720Z"),
    "question" : "How important is networking for career success as a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8942b30e99eeabcd468d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-can-I-do-to-set-myself-on-to-a-career-path-as-a-lawyer?-",
    "answer" : "Probably the best thing for you would be to find out what lawyers actually do. There is a vast variety of careers in the field of law. Some of them might entail the kind of work and activity you would enjoy, and some might be uninteresting or even repugnant to you. You ought to have a good knowledge of what is involved in various legal careers, before you decide to embark on such a career path. However, if you find good reason to decide to become a lawyer, then the most important thing for you to do fight now would be to maximize your academic performance in high school. Try to get into the best college or university you can find. Many different college majors can provide a suitable basis for law school. There are actually pre-law curriculums. Many people intending to go to law school study e Continue Reading Probably the best thing for you would be to find out what lawyers actually do. There is a vast variety of careers in the field of law. Some of them might entail the kind of work and activity you would enjoy, and some might be uninteresting or even repugnant to you. You ought to have a good knowledge of what is involved in various legal careers, before you decide to embark on such a career path. However, if you find good reason to decide to become a lawyer, then the most important thing for you to do fight now would be to maximize your academic performance in high school. Try to get into the best college or university you can find. Many different college majors can provide a suitable basis for law school. There are actually pre-law curriculums. Many people intending to go to law school study e Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:27:14.765Z"),
    "question" : "What can I do to set myself on to a career path as a lawyer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c89f5b30e99eeabcd46d3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-my-career-opportunities-as-a-non-lawyer-holding-a-LLM-degree?-",
    "answer" : "The Juris Doctor (JD) degree used to be known as the Bachelor of Laws (LLB) and is the entry degree for an attorney to join the profession.  It's a generalist degree, containing courses from a wide variety of legal topics.  It's designed to enable you to pass the bar exam and be licensed to practice law.  It typically requires about 90 semester hours of coursework.  Because it takes about three years and equivalent study to other doctoral programs, the American Bar Association changed the degree designation about 35 years ago to Juris Doctor.  The LLM is the Master of Laws degree and is where you enter some specialty field of law as mentioned in the spam above.  An LLM is often 35-45 semester hours of study.  Most LLM programs require the JD for admission to the program. Law is the only  Continue Reading The Juris Doctor (JD) degree used to be known as the Bachelor of Laws (LLB) and is the entry degree for an attorney to join the profession.  It's a generalist degree, containing courses from a wide variety of legal topics.  It's designed to enable you to pass the bar exam and be licensed to practice law.  It typically requires about 90 semester hours of coursework.  Because it takes about three years and equivalent study to other doctoral programs, the American Bar Association changed the degree designation about 35 years ago to Juris Doctor.  The LLM is the Master of Laws degree and is where you enter some specialty field of law as mentioned in the spam above.  An LLM is often 35-45 semester hours of study.  Most LLM programs require the JD for admission to the program. Law is the only  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:30:13.437Z"),
    "question" : "What are my career opportunities as a non-lawyer holding a LLM degree? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8a40b30e99eeabcd46ed"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-a-bad-time-to-pursue-a-career-as-a-lawyer-here-in-the-states?-",
    "answer" : "I would add that it depends on several factors, not all of which are knowable in advance. It depends on whether or not you can get into a top 25 law school, it depends on whether or not you can graduate in the top 25% (or better) in your law school class, it depends on what area of practice you are interested in. Just as an example, if you have an undergraduate degree (or, better yet, a post-graduate degree) in a high-tech science, microbiology, genetics, electrical engineering, etc., AND you have a desire to go into patent law (which is a hot area right now), then you can probably do very well. Lawyers who know both patent law and the hard sciences are rare, and much sought after. But if your undergraduate degree is in the humanities and you want to do criminal defense, forget it. Underst Continue Reading I would add that it depends on several factors, not all of which are knowable in advance. It depends on whether or not you can get into a top 25 law school, it depends on whether or not you can graduate in the top 25% (or better) in your law school class, it depends on what area of practice you are interested in. Just as an example, if you have an undergraduate degree (or, better yet, a post-graduate degree) in a high-tech science, microbiology, genetics, electrical engineering, etc., AND you have a desire to go into patent law (which is a hot area right now), then you can probably do very well. Lawyers who know both patent law and the hard sciences are rare, and much sought after. But if your undergraduate degree is in the humanities and you want to do criminal defense, forget it. Underst Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:31:28.428Z"),
    "question" : "Is it a bad time to pursue a career as a lawyer here in the states? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8a7ab30e99eeabcd4700"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-career-can-a-lawyer-have-in-military-service?-",
    "answer" : "Assuming you are asking about U.S military service, normally lawyers serve as lawyers or some other law-related field in all our U.S. military service branches. The pursuit of justice is of utmost importance in our U.S. military, & the rights of service members are held in the highest regard & are defended & supported by top legal minds. Judge Advocate General's Corps, aka JAG or JAG Corps, refers to the legal branch or specialty concerned with military justice & military law. A military lawyer's job is similar to a civilian lawyer in their day-to-day duties. Representing clientele under the jurisdiction of military courts & law is the primary difference. Military lawyers handle a wide variety of legal issues including international law, operations law, environmental law, as well as military Continue Reading Assuming you are asking about U.S military service, normally lawyers serve as lawyers or some other law-related field in all our U.S. military service branches. The pursuit of justice is of utmost importance in our U.S. military, & the rights of service members are held in the highest regard & are defended & supported by top legal minds. Judge Advocate General's Corps, aka JAG or JAG Corps, refers to the legal branch or specialty concerned with military justice & military law. A military lawyer's job is similar to a civilian lawyer in their day-to-day duties. Representing clientele under the jurisdiction of military courts & law is the primary difference. Military lawyers handle a wide variety of legal issues including international law, operations law, environmental law, as well as military Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:32:26.180Z"),
    "question" : "What career can a lawyer have in military service? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8a8eb30e99eeabcd4712"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-careers-to-get-into-nowadays-besides-a-lawyer-or-a-doctor?-",
    "answer" : "Computer science, particularly data security and quantum computing, is going to be beyond huge. Electrical engineering is always a good bet because it is the foundation of our economy. Quantum computing has the potential to change so many things we take for granted, yet, it is a much more nuanced and difficult form of computation than the zeros and ones that form the basis of our current computing architectures. The technology is advancing faster than we realize—the government probably has stuff we won’t see for a decade. I should think that genetics is an area that will be incredibly profitable in the future when we can finally figure out how to engineer proteins and understand cellular machinery well enough to cure metastatic disease. Bioinformatics is being driven by the huge resources of Continue Reading Computer science, particularly data security and quantum computing, is going to be beyond huge. Electrical engineering is always a good bet because it is the foundation of our economy. Quantum computing has the potential to change so many things we take for granted, yet, it is a much more nuanced and difficult form of computation than the zeros and ones that form the basis of our current computing architectures. The technology is advancing faster than we realize—the government probably has stuff we won’t see for a decade. I should think that genetics is an area that will be incredibly profitable in the future when we can finally figure out how to engineer proteins and understand cellular machinery well enough to cure metastatic disease. Bioinformatics is being driven by the huge resources of Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:32:46.582Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best careers to get into nowadays besides a lawyer or a doctor? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8aacb30e99eeabcd4726"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Career-advice-for-a-non-US-lawyer-who-just-moved-permanently-to-the-USA?-",
    "answer" : "Have you considered getting an LLM and then taking the bar exam in the jurisdiction where you want to work? Also, once you’re connected to a law school, you’ll have access to its resources and networks. This can be an expensive path and does not guarantee employment, but it’s a very clearly defined path for people in the US with foreign law degrees.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:33:16.745Z"),
    "question" : "Career advice for a non US lawyer who just moved permanently to the USA? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8af3b30e99eeabcd4749"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Could-hiring-a-real-estate-lawyer-be-the-first-step-into-building-a-successful-career-for-yourself-in-the-real-estate-industry?-",
    "answer" : "I don’t think hiring a lawyer is necessarily the way to get started. Maybe consulting a lawyer or investing expert could be useful but I don’t see the need in hiring. This is what I would do to get started. 1. Educate and Evaluate Yourself The first thing you want to understand before investing is your financial situation. How much do you spend on average per month? Try to reduce expenses before investing to maximize profits. Find out what of a loan you are eligible for. You then have to thoroughly educate yourself about real estate to know what type of investor you want to be. Ask yourself, “am I interested in fixing up properties and selling them (“fix and flip”) or, am I interested in buying ready-homes and renting them out (“buy and hold”)?” If you need a better idea of investment strateg Continue Reading I don’t think hiring a lawyer is necessarily the way to get started. Maybe consulting a lawyer or investing expert could be useful but I don’t see the need in hiring. This is what I would do to get started. 1. Educate and Evaluate Yourself The first thing you want to understand before investing is your financial situation. How much do you spend on average per month? Try to reduce expenses before investing to maximize profits. Find out what of a loan you are eligible for. You then have to thoroughly educate yourself about real estate to know what type of investor you want to be. Ask yourself, “am I interested in fixing up properties and selling them (“fix and flip”) or, am I interested in buying ready-homes and renting them out (“buy and hold”)?” If you need a better idea of investment strateg Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:34:27.133Z"),
    "question" : "Could hiring a real estate lawyer be the first step into building a successful career for yourself in the real estate industry? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8b42b30e99eeabcd4777"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-career-paths-are-open-to-a-disbarred-lawyer-or-a-doctor-who-loses-his-license?-",
    "answer" : "The fact is that other than if the person is disbarred because of a felony conviction, very few lawyers get disbarred. In most states, disbarment is automatic upon conviction for a felony. In other circumstances, the process is: Someone files a complaint.It gets investigated.The disciplinary committee thinks the complaint may be valid.The committee sends the complaint to the lawyer and asks for a response.The lawyer responds disputing the complaint.The committee reviews the response.If it still thinks the complaint may be valid it sends the response to the complainant.The complainant replies.The committee reviews the reply.Assuming it makes sense, the committee files a disbarment lawsuit or motion (depends on the state.)There are some formal motions, briefs, replies, etc., etc.When it is obviContinue Reading The fact is that other than if the person is disbarred because of a felony conviction, very few lawyers get disbarred. In most states, disbarment is automatic upon conviction for a felony. In other circumstances, the process is: Someone files a complaint.It gets investigated.The disciplinary committee thinks the complaint may be valid.The committee sends the complaint to the lawyer and asks for a response.The lawyer responds disputing the complaint.The committee reviews the response.If it still thinks the complaint may be valid it sends the response to the complainant.The complainant replies.The committee reviews the reply.Assuming it makes sense, the committee files a disbarment lawsuit or motion (depends on the state.)There are some formal motions, briefs, replies, etc., etc.When it is obviContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:35:46.942Z"),
    "question" : "What career paths are open to a disbarred lawyer or a doctor who loses his license? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}